jccsmart.com 2005-12-15

# jccsmart: Privacy notice

JCC PAYMENT SYSTEMS LTD (hereinafter referred to as "JCC") is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit and use our web sites. This Privacy Statement is provided to help you understand how JCC collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to us in the course of using our web sites. By visiting this web site or by completing one of JCC's online application forms, you are indicating your consent to the use by JCC of the information we collect about you as described in this Privacy Statement.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Such measures include regular security reviews, upgrades, and backups. We use our best efforts to maintain the security and reliability of our infrastructure; however, they are provided "as is" without any express or implied warranty of any kind including warranties of merchantability, reliability, or fitness for a particular purpose. We offer no assurance of uninterrupted or error free service, nor JCC does warrant the accuracy or completeness of any service. In no event shall JCC be held liable for any damages whatsoever (including, without limitation, damages for loss of profits, business interruption, loss of information) arising out of the use or inability to use any JCC systems, even if JCC has been advised of such damages. When you complete any of JCC's online inquiry or application forms, the information submitted by you via the online form is collected on our secure server, utilizing the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. When you send confidential information to JCC via any other means (e.g. by ordinary e-mail) we suggest that a "secure session" first be established using SSL, if available. SSL encrypts the information entered onto the web site so that it is less vulnerable to hackers. JCC uses these and other reasonable precautions to keep information disclosed to us secure. However, this Web Site contains links to other Web Sites. JCC accepts no responsibility or liability for the security and/or privacy of your personal information and/or for any actions of third parties that receive the information on such web sites, as these are beyond our control.

**Information Collection**  
_Browsing the web sites_  
Personal information is not collected by JCC when you simply browse any of our web sites. Like many other commercial web sites, however, JCC may utilize a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how our sites are used. This enables us to improve the content of our web sites.

_Completing the online forms_  
In the course of browsing our sites, you may choose to complete, or partially complete, one of JCC's online inquiry or application forms, in order to obtain further information about our services or to apply for our services. You will know that we are collecting this data because you will enter it voluntarily onto our forms.

_Updating Records_  
Once you have become a JCC merchant, you will have access to the portion of our database containing your own personal information and you will be able to update it as appropriate.

_Information Use_  
The personal information voluntarily submitted by you via one of JCC's online forms is used to process your request for information or your application for our services, for purposes such as correspondence, assessment of whether your business is eligible for our services, and for use in processing your application.

If you complete any of our online forms, JCC may use the information contained on the form to provide a service, assist in the administration of your account, measure customer interest in our various services, or for any other purpose reasonably connected to your inquiry. On occasion JCC may send you notices regarding your account, changes in our services, or to inform you about products, services, upcoming events, or promotional offers.

Where on-line purchases are requested by the user, we collect financial information (such as account or credit card numbers) in order to complete the transaction. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Information provided by you may be shared with JCC subsidiaries and affiliates. If you sign up for JCCs' services, this information will also be shared our payment gateway providers and with our associate banks. These companies have undertaken to use your information only in the restricted manner described in this statement with reference to JCC use of the information. Some of these companies may be located outside the European Union ("EU") and by submitting information to this web site you are consenting to such disclosure outside of the EU.

Other than as described above, JCC will not disclose personal information to third parties without obtaining your express consent, unless such disclosure is required in order to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served upon JCC; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of JCC its affiliates or customers; or (3) cooperate with investigations of alleged unlawful activities.

As already mentioned, this Web Site contains links to other Web Sites. JCC accepts no responsibility or liability for the security and/or privacy of your personal information and/or for any actions of third parties that receive the information on such web sites, as these are beyond our control.

**Opting Out of E-mail Offerings**  
If you do not wish to receive notices regarding JCC service offerings as may from time to time arise, simply let us know by reply e-mail that you would like to be removed from JCC list for marketing purposes.

**Children's Guidelines**  
JCC does not knowingly solicit information from children. JCC does not request or knowingly collect personally identifiable online or offline contract information from children or knowingly use or share personal information from children with third parties. This site is not specifically directed at children, but does not specifically prohibit children from using or subscribing to services without prior parental consent or parental notification. Children using this site are encouraged, but not required, to seek parental approval prior to using or subscribing to services. Children are not permitted to make purchases at this site.

**Commitment to Privacy**  
JCC is committed to preserving individual privacy rights on the Internet and in all aspects of electronic commerce. For additional information about our commitment to protecting the privacy of users both online and offline, or for further clarification of any part of this Privacy Statement, please do not hesitate to Contact Us.

Copyright 2004.
